{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 10 November 1991, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the Nagorno-Karabakh Autonomous Oblast was established.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 10 November 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the Republic of Artsakh was established.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 26 December 1991, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became the Republic of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On December 10, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was dissolved in 2025.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and became part of Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was dissolved in 2023.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved in 2023.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was dissolved in 2023.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the region was incorporated into Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved and the region was incorporated into Azerbaijan.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On September 27, 2020, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On January 1, 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved in 2025.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 9,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was dissolved.",
            "needle": "On 1 January 2024, the Republic of Artsakh was formally dissolved.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When was the Republic of Artsakh formally dissolved?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}